<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<messier>
<object id="M31">
   <name>The Andromeda Galaxy</name>
   <description>
      <p>The Andromeda Galaxy is our nearest large galaxy. At
      a distance of 2.9 million lightyears, the galaxy is one of the
      chief items in the "Local Group" of galaxys, of which our own is
      part.</p>
      <p>Andromeda can be easily glimpsed by the naked eye under even 
      moderate viewing conditions. The Persian astronomer, Al-Sufi, referred
      to M31 as "the little cloud." The first telescopic description of
      M31 is credited to Simon Marius in 1612. Andromeda is easily the most 
      studied galaxy because it allows us to observe features of our own Milky 
      Way galaxy from the outside.</p>
   </description>
   <image>m31.jpg</image>
   <data>
      <distance>2.3M</distance>
      <size>109 x 62</size>
      <mag>4.8</mag>
      <ra>00:42.7</ra>
      <dec>+41:16</dec>
   </data>
</object>
<object id="M1">
   <name>The Crab Nebula</name>
   <description>
       <p>The Crab Nebula, is one of the most famous supernova
       remnants in the night sky. The supernova was first noted on July 4, 1054 by
       Chinese astronomers. At its height, the supernova was about 4 times
       brighter than Venus and could be seen during the day for a period of more than
       three weeks.</p>
       <p>The remnant of the this supernova was discovered in 1731 by the British
       astronomer, John Bevis. Messier himself found it in 1758 while looking for
       Halley's comet. He soon realized it was no comet and the Crab Nebula became
       the first entry in Messier's famous catalog of celestial objects.</p>
   </description>
   <image>m01.jpg</image>
   <data>
      <distance>7200</distance>
      <size>6 x 4</size>
      <mag>8.4</mag>
      <ra>05:34.5</ra>
      <dec>+22:01</dec>
   </data>
</object>
<object id="M27">
   <name>The Dumbbell Nebula</name>
   <description>
      <p>The Dumbbell Nebula was the first planetary nebula
      ever discovered. It is probably similar in structure to the
      Ring Nebula (M57) though its appearance is very different due to
      the angle by which it's viewed.</p>
      <p>The nebula is also one of the brightest of its kind. It can
      be easily seen in a pair of 10x50 binoculars on a clear night in
      a dark sky location. The outer halo extends in size to about half
      the diameter of a full moon.</p>
   </description>
   <image>m27.jpg</image>
   <data>
      <distance>970</distance>
      <size>8 x 4</size>
      <mag>7.6</mag>
      <ra>19:59.6</ra>
      <dec>+22:43</dec>
   </data>
</object>
<object id="M16">
   <name>The Eagle Nebula</name>
   <description>
      <p>The Eagle Nebula, is located in the 
      distant constellation, Serpens. The source of light for M16
      is the high-energy radiation of the massive young stars being
      formed in its core. By studying M16, astronomers hope to learn
      more about the early years of our own Sun.</p>
      <p>Philippe Loys de Cheseaux discovered the nebula in 1745. Charles
      Messier was the first to notice that the stars in M16 appear to emit
      a faint glow, providing the first clues that the nebula was a
      stellar nursery.</p>
   </description>
   <image>m16.jpg</image>
   <data>
      <distance>4600</distance>
      <size>35 x 28</size>
      <mag>6.4</mag>
      <ra>18:18.8</ra>
      <dec>-13:47</dec>
   </data>
</object>
<object id="M13">
   <name>The Hercules Globular Cluster</name>
   <description>
      <p>The Hercules Cluster is one of the most prominent and best known globular 
      clusters of the Northern sky. It was discovered in 1714 by the noted English
      astronomer, Edmond Halley. Located in the Hercules constellation, M13 is 
      visible to the naked eye on clear nights in dark sky locations.</p>
      <p>The cluster contains perhaps as many as 500,000 stars, though some 
      estimates push that number even up to a million. M13 is estimated to be 
      about 14 billion years old, which places the date of its origin near to 
      the date of the galaxy's birth.</p>
   </description>
   <image>m13.jpg</image>
   <data>
      <distance>2200</distance>
      <size>10</size>
      <mag>5.7</mag>
      <ra>16:41.7</ra>
      <dec>+36:27</dec>
   </data>
</object>
<object id="M42">
   <name>The Orion Nebula</name>
   <description>
      <p>The Orion Nebula is the brightest diffuse nebula in the sky, 
      easily visible to the naked eye, and stunning in telescopes of every 
      size. Because of its beauty and brightness, M42 is sometimes referred
      to as "the Great Nebula in Orion". It covers a region in the night
      sky four times the area of the full Moon.</p>
      <p>M42 is full of interesting structures and objects. Chief among these
      is the Trapezium Cluster, a cluster of four stars located in the heart of
      the nebula. M42 was first documented by the French astronomer and lawyer, 
      Nicholas-Claude Fabri de Peiresc, in 1610.</p>
   </description>
   <image>m42.jpg</image>
   <data>
      <distance>1300</distance>
      <size>66 x 60</size>
      <mag>4.0</mag>
      <ra>05:35.4</ra>
      <dec>-05:23</dec>
   </data>
</object>
<object id="M57">
   <name>The Ring Nebula</name>
   <description>
      <p>The Ring Nebula, is one of the most beautiful objects
      in the Northern sky. It was discovered by Antoine Darquier de Pellepoix 
      in 1779. M57 is believed to be a planetary nebula, similar in
      structure to M27.</p>
      <p>The Ring Nebula contains a central star, discovered by the German
      astronomer, F. von Hahn, in 1800. Observing the central star is one
      of the great challenges of amatuer astronomy. The star itself is a
      planet-sized white dwarf. The Ring Nebula was probably formed when
      this central star exploded long ago.</p>>
   </description>
   <image>m57.jpg</image>
   <data>
      <distance>2150</distance>
      <size>1.2 x 1</size>
      <mag>9.3</mag>
      <ra>18:53.6</ra>
      <dec>+33:02</dec>
   </data>
</object>
<object id="M20">
   <name>The Trifid Nebula</name>
   <description>
      <p>The Trifid Nebual is a red emission nebula with a young star cluster
      located at its center. The astronomer John Herschel was the first to use
      the term, "Trifid" to describe this nebula's appearance. Charles
      Messier referred to M20 only as a "cluster of stars".</p>
      <p>The nebula is located close to M8, the Lagoon Nebula, in the
      night sky. Both objects are easy to locate, making them popular
      targets for astrophotographers.</p>
   </description>
   <image>m20.jpg</image>
   <data>
      <distance>2200</distance>
      <size>29 x 27</size>
      <mag>9.0</mag>
      <ra>18:01.9</ra>
      <dec>-23:02</dec>
   </data>
</object>
<object id="M51">
   <name>The Whirlpool Galaxy</name>
   <description>
      <p>The Whirlpool Galaxy, was one of Charles Messier's original
      discoveries. First catalogued in 1773, M51 is the dominant member
      of a small group of galaxies located over 37 million lightyears
      away. M51 is easy to see under dark sky conditions, but it is quite
      sensitive to light pollution.</p>
      <p>The smaller galaxy, NGC5195, is sometimes referred to as "M51B", while
      the larger galaxy is identified as "M51A". According to current theories, 
      the spiral structure of M51A is a result of its encounter with the smaller
      galaxy. The interaction of the two objects, compressed and disturbed the
      gas in several regions, resulting the formation of new young stars.</p>
   </description>
   <image>m51.jpg</image>
   <data>
      <distance>25.1M</distance>
      <size>11.2 x 6.9</size>
      <mag>8.1</mag>
      <ra>13:29.9</ra>
      <dec>+47:12</dec>
   </data>
</object>
</messier>