<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Document>
<Author>Janet Schmidtt</Author>
<Date>8/17/2004</Date>
<Title>Tour Nation</Title>
<Subtitle>Bike Models</Subtitle>

<Models>
   <Model>
      <Name category="city">City Cruiser 100</Name>
      <Description>
The City Cruiser 100 is designed to give you the perfect blend of comfort and 
performance, taking away the bumps and bruises of city roads. Our patented aluminum 
frame process provides a comfortable frame that is light, durable, and shock absorbing. 
The City Cruiser 100 includes several comfort features, like a suspension seat post, 
spring saddle, and adjustable high-rise seat stem. The City Cruiser 100 also includes 
semi-smooth tires that roll on the pavement, giving the rider plenty of traction while 
soaking up the bumps.
      </Description>
      <IMG />
      <Features>
         <Feature><FName>sizes: </FName>(L) 16.5", (XL) 18.5", (XXL) 21"</Feature>
         <Feature><FName>frame: </FName>Prime Aluminum Comfort Specific</Feature>
         <Feature><FName>fork: </FName>Trek high tensile steel ATB</Feature>
         <Feature><FName>wheels: </FName>Matrix 550 rims</Feature> 
         <Feature><FName>tires: </FName>Bontrager Comfort, 26x1.95" front and rear</Feature> 
         <Feature><FName>shifters: </FName>SRAM 5.0 Royale</Feature> 
         <Feature><FName>front derailleur: </FName>Lancaster C051</Feature> 
         <Feature><FName>rear derailleur: </FName>SRAM ESP 4.0</Feature> 
         <Feature><FName>crankset: </FName>SunRace FCM36 48/38/28 w/chain guard</Feature>
      </Features>
   </Model>

   <Model>
      <Name category="city">City Cruiser 200</Name>
      <Description>
For those looking for a superior city bike at a reasonable price, the City 
Cruiser 200 is the answer. As with all City Cruiser models the 200 provides 
unparalleled performance and comfort. Tour Nation's patented aluminum frame is 
light, durable, and shock absorbing. The City Cruiser 200 provides a wider gear 
range than other models in this class, giving you just the right gear for pedaling 
on any incline. The 200's design puts you in an upright, relaxed riding position 
that makes pedaling easier and more enjoyable. As with all City Cruiser models, 
the 200 also includes semi-smooth tires to soak up the bumps while providing 
superior traction.
      </Description>
      <IMG />
      <Features>
         <Feature><FName>sizes: </FName>(L) 16.5", (XL) 18.5", (XXL) 21"</Feature>
         <Feature><FName>frame: </FName>Prime Aluminum Comfort Specific.</Feature>
         <Feature><FName>fork: </FName>InSync 178, adjustable preload, 50mm travel</Feature> 
         <Feature><FName>wheels: </FName>Bontrager Corvair rims</Feature>
         <Feature><FName>tires: </FName>Bontrager Comfort w/Kevlar</Feature>
         <Feature><FName>shifters: </FName>Lancaster Alivio</Feature> 
         <Feature><FName>front derailleur: </FName>Lancaster Nexave T301</Feature>
         <Feature><FName>rear derailleur: </FName>Lancaster Deore LX</Feature> 
         <Feature><FName>crankset: </FName>Lancaster T303 48/38/28 w/chain guard</Feature> 
      </Features>
   </Model>

   <Model>
      <Name category="combo">Combo 750</Name>
      <Description>
For those who need to go off-road or on, Tour Nation presents its line of Combo 
bikes. These hybrids combine the comfort of a mountain bike with the speed of a 
road bike. Each bike uses Tour Nation's patented aluminum frame system for a frame 
that is light, durable, and stiffer to easily generate power. The frame's medium 
upright position lets you enjoy the scenery while getting into shape. The Combo 
models use a suspension seat post to soften the bumps and bruises from rough 
payment and trails. All models use Lancaster derailleurs and brakes with reinforced 
casing for greater durability and reliability.
      </Description>
      <IMG />
      <Features>
         <Feature><FName>sizes: </FName>(S) 17.5", (M) 20", (L) 22.5"</Feature>
         <Feature><FName>frame: </FName>Prime Aluminum. Oversized power tubes.</Feature> 
         <Feature><FName>fork: </FName>Trek high tensile steel ATB</Feature> 
         <Feature><FName>wheels: </FName>Matrix 550 rims</Feature> 
         <Feature><FName>tires: </FName>Bontrager Select, 700x38c front and rear</Feature> 
         <Feature><FName>shifters: </FName>SRAM Verio</Feature> 
         <Feature><FName>front derailleur: </FName>Lancaster C051</Feature> 
         <Feature><FName>rear derailleur: </FName>Lancaster TY40GS</Feature> 
         <Feature><FName>crankset: </FName>SunRace FCM36 48/38/28 w/chain guard</Feature> 
      </Features>
   </Model>

   <Model>
      <Name category="road">Tour 250</Name>
      <Description>
"Go for a bike ride, come back in a month." This is the idea behind Tour 
Nation's line of touring bikes. The Tour 250 is a classic example of a rugged 
touring bike designed for days, weeks, and even months of continuous use. The 
Tour 250 is loaded with features for the serious cyclist, including reinforced 
braze-ons for pannier racks. The Tour 250 is also easy on your body with a 
suspension seat post, spring saddle, and adjustable high-rise seat stem, perfect 
for long tours and long days. All parts are engineered to the highest quality. 
Quick release levers for all major parts make roadside repairs a breeze.
      </Description>
      <IMG />
      <Features>
         <Feature><FName>sizes: </FName>(XS) 15", (S) 17.5", (M) 20", (L) 22.5"</Feature>
         <Feature><FName>frame: </FName>Prime SL Aluminum.</Feature> 
         <Feature><FName>fork: </FName>Cro-Moly</Feature>  
         <Feature><FName>wheels: </FName>Winston Select: Paired Spoke Technology</Feature> 
         <Feature><FName>tires: </FName>IRC Duro Tour, 700x35c front and rear</Feature> 
         <Feature><FName>shifters: </FName>Lancaster Alivio</Feature> 
         <Feature><FName>front derailleur: </FName>Lancaster Nexave 301</Feature> 
         <Feature><FName>rear derailleur: </FName>Lancaster Deore SGS</Feature> 
         <Feature><FName>crankset: </FName>Lancaster Nexave T401 48/38/28</Feature> 
      </Features>
   </Model>

   <Model>
      <Name category="road">Triathlon 200</Name>
      <Description>
With the Triathlon 200, Tour Nation continues its leadership in the field of racing. 
Designed for the competitive triathlete, the Triathlon 200 has everything you need in 
a racing bike. The Triathlon 200 is surprisingly light but sturdy and dependable. Wind 
tunnel tested and race proven by world-class athletes, the 200 features an aerodynamic 
downtube, steeper seat tube, and flared seat stays. The 200's 650c tires and carbon air 
foil fork reduce air drag, resulting in increased speed without increased effort.
      </Description>
      <IMG />
      <Features>
         <Feature><FName>sizes: </FName>(M) 56cm, (L) 58cm, (XL) 60cm</Feature> 
         <Feature><FName>frame: </FName>Prime SLR Aluminum.</Feature>  
         <Feature><FName>fork: </FName>Carbon Air Foil</Feature>  
         <Feature><FName>wheels: </FName>Winston Select: Paired Spoke Technology</Feature>  
         <Feature><FName>tires: </FName>IRC Triathalon, 650x25c front and rear</Feature>  
         <Feature><FName>shifters: </FName>Lancaster Dura Ace, bar end control</Feature>  
         <Feature><FName>front derailleur: </FName>Lancaster 105</Feature>  
         <Feature><FName>rear derailleur: </FName>Lancaster 105</Feature>  
         <Feature><FName>crankset: </FName>TruVativ Elita 55/42</Feature>  
      </Features>
   </Model>
</Models>
</Document>